# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Klomegah Leo

Gender: Male

Nationality: Ghanaian Hometown: Agbozume

Languages spoken: English, Ewe, French

Email: leoklomegah8@gmail.com

Telephone: 0544993066

### CAREER OBJECTIVES/ PERSONAL PROFESSIONAL QUALITIES

I'm determined to work for a company that will help me advance both personally and technically so I can compete with the greatest software developers in the world. I've worked both individually and with a team in a time-constrained setting, and I have outstanding management and leadership skills. I love working as a team and have a flexible schedule.

#### EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Ho Technical University January, 2023 - till date

**BTech Information Communication Technology** 

Ho Technical University September, 2020 - June 2023

**HND Information Communication Technology** 

Keta Senior High Technical school September, 2016 - June, 2019

WASSCE (General Science)

Aflao Basic School (Ghanasco) 2005 - June 2016

(BECE)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

November 2023 - till date

National Service at NodeEight

- 1. Learned web development with JavaScript and React Framework
- 2. Built different User Interface with reactJs and Javascript

3.

May 2022 - August 2022

Internship with NodeEight Hub

- 1. Worked in the Media department for a month and half
- 2. Later worked in the media department for a month

#### **SOME PERSONAL PROJECTS**

https://personal-portfolio-taupe-ten-97.vercel.app/

A link to my portfolio

## **SPECIAL SKILLS**

- 1. Team player
- 2. Interpersonal communication
- 3. Teaching